<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Kids Ruby</title>
  <subtitle>Blog</subtitle>
  <id>http://kidsruby.com/</id>
  <link href="http://kidsruby.com/"/>
  <link href="http://kidsruby.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-07-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>KidsRuby Site has a New Look</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2014-07-30-kidskuby-site-has-a-new-look.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2014-07-30-kidskuby-site-has-a-new-look.html</id>
    <published>2014-07-30T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-08-23T12:35:30-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	It's been a while since our last post and sorry we have not been on top of keeping all of you in the loop, but we are returning better than ever! We've just finished reworking our entire site and gave it a new look. Now if you are interested in contributing to KidsRuby you can visit the &lt;a href="contribute.html"&gt;Contribute&lt;/a&gt; page to create lessons of your own or submit new tranlations to help teach Ruby to those regardless of their country or language!  Become a KidsRuby contributor and join us in helping teach programming all around the world!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="article"&gt; 
	 A lot has been going on for the past year that we have not had a chance to properly share. Perhaps the most exciting news to come out this past year was when we won the &lt;a href="http://www.myfukuoka.com/uncategorized/2013-fukuoka-ruby-award-winners.html"&gt;2013 Fukuoma Award&lt;/a&gt;! The Fukuoka Award was created in collaboration with Ruby founder "Matz" to recognize those who have done great things with Ruby. It feels great to get the vindication that KidsRuby is doing something special!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="article"&gt; 
	Earlier this year we were given the opportunity to do a class at &lt;a href="http://www.socallinuxexpo.org/scale12x"&gt;SCaLE 12x&lt;/a&gt;, and it was the first time we were able to test out an early alpha version of KidsRuby 2! Everyone in the class had a great time and it was amazing to see how quickly the kids picked up and excelled with Ruby. It was all a lot of fun and many thanks to the organizers and volunteers who helped us ensure that the class went smoothly.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="article"&gt; 
	We are pushing forward with development of KidsRuby version 2.0. It will be full of many awesome new features and some much needed fixes to the program's core. This means KidsRuby will be even more robust with greater accessibility to a bigger audience, opening up many new and exciting possibilities! The future is looking bright for KidsRuby so keep your eye on us. In the meantime, get coding! 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>KidsRuby Robot Edition&amp;#58; New Release With Support For Sphero Robots, Ubuntu, and Raspberry Pi</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2013-01-15-kidskuby-robot-edition-new-release-with-support-for-sphero-robots-ubuntu-and-raspberry-pi.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2013-01-15-kidskuby-robot-edition-new-release-with-support-for-sphero-robots-ubuntu-and-raspberry-pi.html</id>
    <published>2013-01-15T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T15:13:55-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	We've just released the latest KidsRuby version 1.3, and we're very excited to announce built-in support for the Sphero robotic ball from Orbotix (&lt;a href="http://gosphero.com/" target="blank"&gt;http://gosphero.com/&lt;/a&gt;). If you were at RubyConf in Denver you might have seen the preview, and now we've got everything you need to get started learning about the wonderful world of robotics! Support for more robots coming soon...
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	In addition, we now have the standalone KidsRuby Installer for Raspberry Pi (Raspbian), and KidsRuby Installer for Debian, including Ubuntu and other Debian-based Linux versions. Get them while they're hot from our download page at &lt;a href="http://kidsruby.com/download.html"&gt;http://kidsruby.com/download.html&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>KidsRuby Studies Abroad&amp;#58; Now Available In Japanese, French, and Spanish!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2012-09-06-kidsruby-studies-abroad-now-available-in-japanese-french-and-spanish.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2012-09-06-kidsruby-studies-abroad-now-available-in-japanese-french-and-spanish.html</id>
    <published>2012-09-06T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T15:13:55-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	Our brand new 1.2 release of KidsRuby has gone international, now with full Japanese, French, and Spanish translations. That means our unique and fun way to learn programming has been localized so even more kids all over the world can have fun coding in in Ruby. Thank you to the translators and dev team who helped make this new release possible!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Twin Cities Hosts KidsRuby In Minneapolis, MN At KidsCodeCamp Before JRubyConf Conference 2012</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2012-05-20-the-twin-cities-hosts-kidsruby-in-minneapolis-mn-at-kidscodecamp-before-jrubyconf-conference-2012.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2012-05-20-the-twin-cities-hosts-kidsruby-in-minneapolis-mn-at-kidscodecamp-before-jrubyconf-conference-2012.html</id>
    <published>2012-05-20T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T15:13:55-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	Our kids programming class on May 20 in Minneapolis at &lt;a href="http://kidscodecamp.com/"&gt;KidsCodeCamp&lt;/a&gt; in cooperation with JRubyConf 2012 (&lt;a href="http://jrubyconf.com/"&gt;http://jrubyconf.com/&lt;/a&gt;) was incredibly fun. Special thanks to the fantastic local organizers, as well as the awesome kids in attendence!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>KidsRuby and Robots at KidsCodeCamp At STEM Expo 2012 in Pasadena, CA</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2012-05-19-kidsruby-and-robots-at-kidscodecamp-at-stem-expo-2012-in-pasadena-ca.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2012-05-19-kidsruby-and-robots-at-kidscodecamp-at-stem-expo-2012-in-pasadena-ca.html</id>
    <published>2012-05-19T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T15:13:55-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	We had a fantastic KidsRuby class at the &lt;a href="http://kidscodecamp.com/"&gt;KidsCodeCamp&lt;/a&gt; that took place on May 19 in Pasadena, CA in participation with the massive Pasadena STEM Expo 2012 event! Hundreds of kids were in attendance, between our packed classes, the robotics competitions, and the separate exibition hall. Robots everywhere!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>KidsRuby In Austin, TX, At The First KidsCodeCamp Before RailsConf 2012 Conference</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://kidsruby.com/2012-04-22-kidsruby-in-austin-tx-at-the-first-kidscodecamp-before-railsconf-2012-conference.html"/>
    <id>http://kidsruby.com/2012-04-22-kidsruby-in-austin-tx-at-the-first-kidscodecamp-before-railsconf-2012-conference.html</id>
    <published>2012-04-22T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T15:13:55-07:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p class="article"&gt;
	A great time was had by all on April 22, 2012 in Austin, TX. in cooperation with the first KidsCodeCamp (&lt;a href="http://kidscodecamp.com/"&gt;http://kidscodecamp.com/&lt;/a&gt;) event taking place in participation with RailsConf 2012 (&lt;a href="http://railsconf2012.com/"&gt;http://railsconf2012.com/&lt;/a&gt;). Thank you so much to all of the great volunteers and kids!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
